find-bride.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy | Find-Bride.com

**Find-Bride.com** (hereinafter «Website» or «We») values the privacy of all of our users and has established this Privacy Policy to show commitment to these rights and to safeguard your privacy. If you use our website or application or services, then we urge you to read this Privacy Policy and become fully informed about how it affects to your personal privacy. Please refer to this Privacy Policy to find out how to contact us if you have any questions about the contents herein. By using our website you consent to the contents of this Privacy Policy.

Contents:

I. Privacy Policy  
II. Types of personal data collected  
III. The use and share of the collected personal data  
IV. Age restriction  
V. The rights of access and opt-out  
VI. Mode and place of processing the personal data  
VII. Retention time and deletion of personal data  
VIII. Changes to this privacy policy  
IX. Acceptance of this privacy policy

I. Privacy Policy  
When you visit any website, you are providing a range of personal information about your visit to the operators of the website, depending on the actions you take. This is also the case with Find-Bride.com. You should always understand the privacy policies on any website when supplying information during your use of the website. You should always ask for a copy of the privacy policy if the website does not make the information available to you.

We will only use the personal data you send to us during your visits for the purposes of internal tracking. This includes the activities of making Find-Bride.com and other our websites more effective for you to use our website’s features and services and responding appropriately to your requests for information. Unless specifically mentioned, we do not use your personal data for any other reason. We will never sell your personal data to a third party, and we will never give a third party access to your personal data, except as may be provided in our Terms of Use Agreement or Privacy Policy or unless required to do so by law.

II. Types of personal data collected  
Personal data requests and user registration

When you use or register on the Find-Bride.com website, we only collect personal data that you provide of your own accord. It is possible to browse our website without registering, but you will need to register for the purpose of using certain features and services that we offer. By registering on our website you will provide and share your personal data with the public and with other users. Something that is public can be seen by anyone. For example, the personal data you provide in section «Profile», your name, last name, gender, username, user ID, profile picture, country, and photos. This personal data is made available to the public to help connect you with other website users. Please be advised that public personal data can show up when someone does a search on Find-Bride.com or on another search engine. In some cases, people you share and communicate with may download or copy the content you provided to them or make it public. Use caution about the personal data you share with others.

Personal data you provide us when you use our services or register for an account with us:

  * identifying personal data such as your gender, email and billing address when you register for an account with us. It is your voluntary decision whether to provide us with any such personal information, but if you refuse to provide such information we may not be able to register you to receive our services;
  * other content that you generate, or that is connected to your account (username, user ID, profile picture, photos and videos, interests, favorites);
  * phone number and financial personal data (such as credit card number) if you use the relevant services;
  * you may also provide us other personal data through your participation in user-to-user communications, chats, or when you otherwise communicate with us regarding our services;
  * additional personal data we are required or authorized by applicable laws to collect and process in order to authenticate or identify you or to verify the personal data we have collected.

Personal data we collect automatically when you use our services or register for an account with us:  
we collect data about your interaction with our services and your communications with us. This is personal data we receive from devices (including mobile devices) you use when you access our services. This personal data could include the following: device type, operating system, IP address, User agent, platform, anonymous User ID, Google Advertiser ID, device model, manufacture, OS version, network status (WiFi/3G), Login source, notification status, registration date, credits bought, date of last payment and use of services;  
location personal data, including location personal data from your mobile device including specific geographic locations through IP, GPS, Bluetooth, or WiFi signals;  
computer and connection personal data such as statistics on your page views, traffic to and from the websites, referral URL, ad data, your IP address, your browsing history, and your web log personal data;

Personal data we collect using cookies and similar technologies:

We use cookie technology on Find-Bride.com as part of the statistical reporting on our website. It contains personal data used by a website to personalize your experience (e.g. rotating profiles on the Find-Bride.com home page) and to gather statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded during your experience, the domain name and country of the internet provider that you have come from (e.g. ‘aol’, or ‘umich.edu’), and addresses of those websites you have visited just before and after Find-Bride.com. Nevertheless, we do not associate any of this personal data with you as an individual. Only an aggregate measure is taken. Cookie personal data allows us to follow your «click stream» activity (i.e., how visitors navigate our website as they move from page to page). It is important to note that cookies never capture your individual email address or any of your private personal data.

We also operate standard web server log files to assist in counting visitor numbers and analyzing our website’s technical capability. This personal data is used to establish how many people visit Find-Bride.com, enable us to organize the pages for the best usability, make the website suitable for your browser, and ensure that our pages are working at their full potential. Although we collect personal data on website traffic we do not record personal data on particular visitors to our website, which means that no personal data about you as an individual is retained or used. You are able to browse the website without cookies by configuring your browser to reject all cookies, or to alert you when a cookie is sent. Since each browser is different, you should refer to the «Help» menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

Personal data we collect from other social media:

We allow you to create your account with the respective social media site (e.g. Facebook, Google or other). Those social media sites may give us automatic access to certain personal data retained by them about you. You control the personal data you share with us through the respective social media you used for registering account with us privacy settings on the applicable social media site and the permissions you give us when you grant us access to the personal data retained by the respective social media site about you. By associating an account managed by a social media site with your account on our Website and authorizing us to have access to your personal data, you agree that we can collect, use and retain the personal data provided by these social media sites in accordance with this Privacy Policy and privacy policy of respective social media site in part of personal data transfer to us.

III. The use and share of the collected personal data  
We use your personal data to fulfill the provisions of Find-Bride.com Terms of Use Agreement with you and provide you with our services, to comply with our legal obligations and to protect your vital interest. This includes:

  * management of your account and preferences, operate, measure and improve our services, keep our services safe, secure and operational, and customize website content that includes services that you may like in response to actions that you take;
  * provision of customer support, to contact you regarding your account, to resolve any dispute and answer your questions and enquires;

  * provision of marketing information and special offers, different kind of notifications about our services (you have the right to withdraw, opt-out, your consent at any time;
  * provision of analytics, improve services, monitor and develop the personal data security of our website, measure the performance of our marketing and advertising campaigns;
  * detection and protection against fraudulent transactions and other suspicious activities;
  * to create Agregated data for internal use or for improving services/websites and creating new features. Agregated data is anonymous and is not linked to any personal data.
  * Aggregate Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be tailored to customer desires. We may share such aggregated data with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion.

Following links to other websites

If you click on a link that takes you away from Find-Bride.com to another website, you should remember that the Terms of Use Agreement and Privacy Policy of Find-Bride.com no longer apply to the new website you visit. All your activity on any other website, including any website with a link on Find-Bride.com, is subject to the rules and regulations of that website. Therefore, we recommend that you read all the policies of new websites you visit to fully understand their rules and regulations for collecting, using, and sharing your personal data.

We may share your personal data you provide to us with specially selected service providers service providers who assist us in delivering the products and services we offer for the sole purpose of providing the services or when we consider their services or products to be of interest to you. These service providers must adhere to strict confidentiality obligations in a way that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the agreements we enter into with them. We may cooperate with external service providers to:

oversee a customer personal data database;  
help us in sending out emails, sms (message and data rates may apply) and presents;  
help us with direct marketing;  
assist us with storage and data analysis;  
prevent from fraudulent activities;  
help us in maintaining, developing and improving our systems/websites/applications/services;  
collect payments;  
We may transfer or share a copy of your personal data in cases where Find-Bride.com or one of its properties, affiliates, or subsidiaries is part of a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling part of its assets.

The Personal data may be used for legal purposes by us or the Data controller and any of its affiliates, subsidiaries, directors and etc., in court or to protect against the contravention or unauthorized use of our website, to defend or protect our rights.

We may share personal data internally within our family of companies or with third parties for purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Personal data collected within the European Economic Area («EEA») may, for example, be transferred to countries outside of the EEA for the purposes as described in this Privacy Policy. We utilize standard contract clauses approved by the European Commission, adopt other means under European Union law, and obtain your consent to legitimize data transfers from the EEA to the United States and other countries.

By posting any content, messages, photos and/or videos to any public area of the website/ application You automatically grant, represent and warrant that You have the right to grant to Website an irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, fully paid, worldwide license to use, copy, perform, display, and distribute such personal data and content and to prepare derivative works of, or incorporate into other works, such personal data and content, and to grant and authorize sublicenses of the foregoing.

For content that is covered by intellectual property rights, like photos and videos (IP content), you specifically give us the following permission, subject to your privacy and application settings: you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any IP content that you post on or in connection with Website / application (IP License). This IP License ends when you terminate your membership with the Website / application and we according this Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions delete your IP content unless your content has been shared with others, and they have not deleted it.

You can contact us using the contact information provided below with questions or concerns. We also may resolve disputes you have with us in connection with our Privacy Policy.

IV. Age restriction  
Children under 18 years of age are not allowed to use our website and our services are not targeted at children under the age of 18. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, any personal data we receive from users we believe to be aged 18 or under will be removed from our database.

V. The rights of access and opt-out  
You have the right, at any time, to change or delete your Personal data, please carry out these instructions:

Log into your account;  
Click your name at the top left hand corner of the Find-Bride.com main page;  
Select Profile;  
Click the pencil thumbnail in section You would like to edit;  
Edit your personal data.  
You may also send a request to our Support Team and they will guide you through the process.

You can decide which correspondence to receive from us in accordance with our policy on freedom of choice and opting out. To stop receiving correspondence you can click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of each email you receive or by changing the settings in your profile.

VI. Mode and place of processing the personal data  
The Data controller processes the personal data of users of Find-Bride.com in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the personal data.

The personal data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data controller, in some cases, the personal data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Data controller.

The Personal data is processed at the Data controller’s operating offices and in any other place where the parties involved with the processing are located.

VII. Retention time and deletion of personal data  
The Personal data is kept for the time necessary to provide the services to you and you can always request that the Data controller suspend or delete your personal data. If You wish to delete personal data we have collected during your use of Website / application, You should send a request to our Support Team. Processing of your request will take some time to take effect. Thank you for your patience. Please note that changing or deleting your personal data will only change or delete the data in our database for purposes of future activities and for managing future communications. These changes and deletions will not change or delete emails or personal data website / application may have already forwarded to other users or credit card companies or any other third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy. Further, if you delete your personal data from the Website / application, but continue to use other our websites/applications/services, you may receive emails from us regarding those websites/applications/services. However, we may elect to keep your personal data, subject to the requirements of the law and legitimate interests of the Data controller. In case of your request to delete all your personal data, you agree that your email will be stored in our database to avoid creation of duplicate accounts and for identification purposes. The email will not be used in marketing activities, nor forwarded to any partner websites or Third parties.

Please note that, even after termination of membership and deletion of any personal data, termination of any license granted hereunder, some content may continue to exist because of cached internet pages beyond the control of Find-Bride.com.

VIII. Changes to this privacy policy  
Find-Bride.com reserves the right to replace, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at its own discretion. It is your responsibility to review this page and check for any Privacy Policy updates. Please note the latest modification date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy.

IX. Acceptance of this privacy policy  
Our website and your use of it, including any issue concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the related Terms & Conditions. When you use our website, you accept the conditions set out in this Privacy Policy and the related Terms of Use Agreement. You signify and guarantee that you will never generate any databases, websites, software, legal entities and services that compete with Find-Bride.com. Such behavior will be fully investigated, and necessary legal action will be carried out, including, without limitation, civil, criminal, and injunctive redress.

The acceptance of this Privacy Policy and applicable Terms of Use Agreement are considered as a pre-condition for the use of our website/Application and our services.

Last updated May, 2019
